Name: Doraemon 8-1
(Typhoon maker)
HEY
What are you doing?
Sorry, didn't do it
on purpose
That's not right either
Because of people like you
Japan becomes so dirty
I know, I should do this
What should I do then?
On your knee and apology to
the road
Huff)'
Mr. Road, I am sorry
Now, clean the street
Clean...
Finished
Ok, come with me
Why why should I clean
your room
It's part of Japan
so have to clean it
Finished
Thank you so much
Mom, I clean the room now
Nonsense
You've never clean your room
So clean
Wonderful, my son
you clean the room
What did you say?
This is unforgivable
Throw chewing gum randomly
is my fault
But he uses the weakness
What a low class
I want to revenge
How?
Use this
Typhoon maker
Use low pressure air to make
typhoon
So, using typhoon to revenge
Turn on the power
Use the high temperature of
plat to make air go up
Forms the low air pressure
Don't touch it, it's dangerous
Now, the speed is about 20 meters
Heading Jian's house
Rada arrow will lead typhoon
route
Watch rada
leading to Jian's home
Who is that at the lobby so noisy
Next is Nobita house
How did it turn out to like this?
Sorry, Mr. Postman
You're so powerful
Wait, something sound weird
An arrow on the road
Hurts
Now announce the typhoon news
A small typhoon is developing
Heading Jian's room
Finish
What kind of joke is this
I won't let typhoon to come to
my house
Stop, stop, I say don't run
Jian is panicking
Good
Stop, stop
power of typhoon is unbeatable
Dorn,I've to run home to
close door and windows
Dorn...
I won't let you make a
loop home first
I won't loss to that
weird typhoon
Finally catch up
Good, I'm here
Attack
Will never let you in
What a strong door
Any other entry
No use to change place
Dorn, Jian went home and be
prepared
Got it
Become quiet
Typhoon gives up and leave
All right, banzai
It came in from the floor
Jian
Just clean the room
Now it's so messy
You're so helpless
It's all because of the typhoon
Mom misunderstood me
Revenge accomplished
Great
What's wrong with you?
I turned off the power
typhoon still here
What should I do, Doraemon?
The machine seems to be broken
Left without me
Ah, I hate it
Shizuka, I'm sorry
It's terrible
I can't fix it
It's getting bigger
It's getting serious now
Doraemon,
think of something
I give UP
Change direction
Should it be...
Heading toward home ?
What should I do ?
Ah, no
Nobita, what are you doing
No, can't come here
No, don't come
Machine's broken, typhoon
finally disappeared
(A World Does Not Use Money)
No, I knew it
stingy
You always work so hard
for money
Yes, I always work so hard
It'd be so easy if lived in a
world don't use money
You can try it out
Look
All right, even have telephone
booth
Come make a phone call hurry
If a telephone booth can
let people experience things
That's right
Hey, hello
I want to try living in a world
doesn't use money
Please
How about this
The world has already change
into no money world
Yes
Then I should be able to have it
Always dream about having that
Have it for free
Can't believe this
This is it, this is it
I dream about having this remote
combination
Can I take this?
Thank you very much
Wait, wait
What
Trying to take it away like that?
Charge 26000 Yen
I knew it No such nice thing
Impossible of having a world
does not use money
Take it
Take the charge with you
Not only the remote combination
also the money too
This is just ordinary
why so surprise
What a wonderful world
I've been thinking live in a world
like this
Terrible, monthly income is red
again
What should do this month?
Here's 26000 Yen
Take it
Let me be nice boy once
Usually, I ask money from mom
Take it
26000 Yen
You take the money bane
Please, would you think about it
the situation at home
Look
It's real..
L's troubled by saving too much
money
How come
Oh, no
I've got a pickpocket
100000 Yen was put in my pocket
I didn't even know it
What should I do?
I hate this, I don't care now
The economy can't be balanced
Sorry, honey
The end of the month is coming
Company will take my salary
away
But your salary is already so low
WHY
How come
Take money home will be scolded
What is going on here?
I bought a diamond and take
60000000 Yen
You didn't even pay
that's great
You are great
Where
Please masters
Please pitty me
Hey, kid would you just take one
Please
Please take it away
What is going on here ?
No body loves money at all
Why don't you just throw them
away like this
Ah?
So much money here
You can't hurry money there
Why do you get scolded by
throwing money away
Don't run kid
I say don't run away
How are you going to compensate
me
My world class vessel is gone
Brother
Whoever throw away money will
be fined 10 times
Come, take this away
Little brother, you have to
compensate me
You take the 10 billion
But...
Huff)'
Hurry and take it
Money. Money
I hate this, I hate this
Help
Staying here, I'll be crazy
Hey, put the world back to what
it was
Recovered ?
Recovered
Let me see
Give me this
Wait, boy
260000 Yen
Can't take it?
Please pay first
Back to normal now
Back to what it was before
Great
(Up side down)
It's so difficult
So difficult
Don't if there any use
Usage, purpose
8 or 9 out of 10 is no use
but still ask
Nobita, excuse me,
disturbing your study
I'd like to borrow your
intelligence
Be quiet. I'm doing home work
Study just once for a while,
what so big deal
Look, your interruption
making me get this wrong
Really
Just when I want to study
It turned black
This is no good use
Doraemon, look at you have
done
Turning up side down
This
Look like a pointer of clock?
Whatever it touches
will be turning up side down
Look
A broken pencil sharpener
But the pencil grows longer
Try something else to it
The light turned dark
Look, can't use it at all
Throw the thing away
Wait
What a pity to just throw it away
This is quite interesting
Use it right
Can be very helpful
ls it? It's useful ?
Can you think of any purpose ?
All right, use for what?
Use for what purpose ? To do
what?
Say it, tell me
So noisy
Ok, I'll do it
Did you think of anything?
Try it, and will find out the usage
That is it
Use this
Cloths are about to dry
Really, what kind of weird weather
I see the cloths are wet
Try to dry them
Can't do it
I won't give up
Really, ok?
Come
This time, we'll make it
Who knows
Cigarette, cigarette...
What are you two doing
No, nothing
Did you see daddy's cigarette
Over there
Got it
Let me have one
Seems nothing happen
What? What is this?
The more I smoke, the longer it
gets
Look, don't have any use
Should try some more
or hard to tell
Good
What is going on ?
I was about to finish smoking
what's happening
Come
HEY
Starting from beginning
weird things keep coming
Must be Doraemon and
Nobita playing tricks
Nobita, Doraemon, come
over here
Nobita, come here
Didn't I say not to try any more
But...
But what, give it back to me
Throw this away
Doraemon
Doraemon, are you all right?
Bury in the ground
Don't stand on the road
get away
Heysu Heysu
Doraemon is going crazy
Master, it's me confused by the
devil
No, is no
No, means no Can never forgive
you
Doraemon, wait, wait
So, just put it up side down, it
will recovered
Better let everyone recovered
Disturbance has quiet down
And it proves that this is
something of no use
That way, we have waist a lot
Nobita
Don't play trick, do your home
work
I'll do it right away
Can't understand this, it's too
difficult
Right, I know it, use the up
side down method
Stupid brain will be improved
using this
What! This is easy
Smoothly
How boring, the home work is
too easy
Being too smart is not cute at all
It'll cause many problems if
keep this with me
Why don't I hide it inside
Sting myself
Ah?
(Sharing Chewing Gum)
The taste is good
Nobita, desert time
Coming, sorry to keep you waiting
Mom told us to share
Eat
Break it into two
Which side is male, which side is
female
That one over there is a male
Wrong
Lately
Desert is getting worse
A plat of peanuts is just like
what pigeons have
Nobita, too much desert is not
good for health
Mom says so
Actually it was for saving money
I guess so too
Mai
Come PW'!
I'm on my way home
Go play at your house
Don't come, don't come
My mom is cutting the melon
If you come
my share will become less
Bye now
He said melon
So envy him
Follow him home then
Want to take a peek
No, too embarrassing
Even if you peek, I won't give you
Before having melon
Have some of this
But I can only give you one third
Bye
Want to give me, then I'll take it
Made it, made it
The rest of the chewing gum,
one half for each
This is a sharing chewing gum
Suneo is having melon
The smell floats to our mouth
Coming
This is a good melon
Smoothy taste
Smell good and crispy
How sweet
The melon is really good
But the taste is a bit pail
Only one third of the regular one
Taste so good
Right
I feel full now
Ok, Doraemon
please give me the chewing gum
What do you want to do?
Take it
I'll invite everyone to have half
Coming, who is it?
Nobita
What's for dessert today?
I think it should be cake
How nice
Take this chewing gum
What's for dessert today?
I guess it's pancake
Great
This chewing gum
Have half of it please
Wait, you just ate desert
I'm going to eat now
Then give half of the chewing gum
You too
To Jian too
Finish preparation
Good, now you can all have the
delicious tastes
Why did Nobita give me chewing
gum
Will it added some filthy things
I doubt it
The delicious taste coming up
Sweet like cherry and fruits
Cake, what Shizuka is having
And pancake, I love the most
Bake fish
This is good too
Lamein
Hot
Why didn't you blow it before
eating, so hot
Banana
Crashing ice
Ice Cream
Enough, I'm full
Nobita, this is great
Look
Desert is coming
Mom has changed her mind
It's been a while not to treat
you nice desert
So, just make this cake for you
Come it, it's delicious
Not necessary
But I made this specially
for you
Wait for while, I'll eat it
Someone is eating again
Stop, greedy eater
What is this, taste like
spoiled
Licking the chicken bone
Sticky spoiled meat
Stinky cheese
Stop, don't eat
Help
I hate this, don't eat
anything strange
Nobita
I gave the chewing gum to a dog
Fainted
(Secret Treasure of
Nobita Choweiman)
First, from the Bacho Tree
heading east 10 steps
One two three four five six seven
eight nine ten
Turn to west and walk 10 steps
One two three four five six seven
eight nine ten
What, back to where we started
What are you doing Nobita?
Start digging from you stand,
there should be treasure
Did you say treasure
I want to help too, and give me a share
This is my share
Stingy, stingy, super stingy
Why get so excited ?
Finished
It's very special that you found it
So using this way to
get petty money is exciting
Yes
Petty money?
I was too excited, this is too much
After all that effort
only get this much
I really want to find real treasure
This is not that often
Ancestors leave gold to their
offspring
Write down where the treasures are
Daddy
Do we have that kind of old book
Impossible
That's true, it won't be still
here if we had one
Of course we do
Really
Not this one
Not this either
Not yet ?
Hurry and take it out
Got, this is it
Really
Winchen time first of November
About 130 years ago
Nobita Choweiman wrote it
Nobita Choweiman was
the ancestor 6 generation ago
Maybe a Land Lord, rich man
Because saved too much money
so he hurried them
How excited
Location of the treasure is
Where ?
The rest is gone
How can it be like this, daddy
If we knew the location
The treasure would belong gone
I knew it, there's not such
good thing in the world
Wonder where is the treasure now
Buried at...
Let's go, take the time machine to
Winchen time
Just to see where is the treasure
Let's go, go
Here we are
Uh, no
So stink, go to the river and wash
Go gind Nobita Choweiman's
Ask the boy
Look just like Nobita
Are you Nobita Choweiman's..
I'm son of Nobita Choweiman
Acho
Great, we found him
Daddy, we have guests
You're from out of town
smell strange too
May I ask who you are ?
How do I introduce myself
We are you relatives from
very far away
Welcome
Enjoy your time here
I'm going out to take care of
some affairs
Be careful on the way
The bottle is...
Follow him and see
He doesn't look like a rich man
What do you want?
Where are you going ?
We miss you very much, even
we meet the first time
Since you say so, then let's go
home
Didn't you say you want to take
care of something
I can do that later
The house
doesn't look like having any gold
Can't judge the person from his
look
Welcome back
How are you
Atmosphere is quite uneasy
No, be patient and keep them
here
He'll bury the treasure today
Finally started
So, he went to the toilet
Why didn't they go home soon ?
Why can't he be hurry and bury?
It's time for us to go home
You're going home now?
That's too bad
Bye now
Take care
Nobita
Nobita what's wrong with you?
If we are here
he won't bury it
So, let's hide and watch
he'll go bury the treasure
That's why
See, he is out now
There
The scene changed a bit
but it is here
Right, right here
What are you doing ?
How can you dig on the street
randomly ?
We'll fix it right after this
Nop
How can it be
It's a pipe
How weird
I did see him buried the treasure here
That's' right
Must be someone already got it
We should have dig earlier
Go to that time again
Ok
Found it
Finally find it
Just like the map shows
See
this is a fun way to get petty cash
But, it says there are lots of
money, and it's only this much
How terrible
didn’t think ancestors would do the same
Nobita's' family has no progress
( Plan Clock)
Nobita, I often feel kind of strange
You always day dreaming
doing nothing
What is in your brain any way
There're lots of things to do
I was thinking what should I do
What should be done first
Think about this and that...
Then time flys
At the end, I did not do anything
Time is money
You can't waist time
What are you taking out?
Plan clock
You plan your time first
What time should you do what
till when
Then do the next thing
Write it down on the card and
put it in
Then, machine will do those things
for me
No
You are the one to do those things
What? That's boring
Don't go
I want to correct your problem
Ok, don't be angry then
Ay, what should I write down?
First, study
2:30 to 6:30
Study for this long ! I'll die
Then how about 30 minutes
After dark
Study till 3 o'clock
3 o'clock start desert time
And go to the toilet too
3:30
I want to watch TV
And then go out to play baseball
Once finish the pan card, put it in
The card won't git in
Huff)'
Hold it straight
See
Start moving now
It's 2:30, time to study
This is Nobita's plan
Why should I do it
Hurry hurry
Ok, clock will ask the person put
the card in to do things
Ok, desert is here
Red bean cake
I'm eating now
It hurts
Not yet
The machine is so nice
Sorry, I ate all your too
Too much, this is too much
Study, study
It's 3 o'clock
Time to have desert
There's no desert left
No desert, but still want to eat
You have to follow the plan
Chew and swallow
Ah, so dumb
3:20 go to the toilet
Even if you don't want to go
still have to do it?
At this play doing nothing
feel like a idiot
Feel kind of emptiness
Ok, finish
Now, watch TV
I don't want to watch at all
The TV is broken
That's ok
Then play baseball
Finally can leave the plan alone
and play heartly
It's raining
You're right
Even it's raining, still have to play ?
Right
It that right
No one is here
Time is up
Play baseball by yourself
I know, I know
Ah, playing ball in the rain
Good catch
Doraemon loves to play
baseball
What are you talking about?
Dorn, I don't want to play now
Don't run away
Do things as scheduled
Where should I run to ?
If I go home, I'll be caught
Please, let me hid here
You can't run away
I'll find you
And tell you to do things as
planned
No matter where you are
I'll find you
Next, painting with big sister
can I
This way
Doraemon ?
I don't know
Lair
The needle will find where he is
Here
In here
It hurts
6 o'clock, time to have dinner
I know, go home to have dinner
Can't get home in time
Hurry, to be home and eat
Just fot the plan
You have to eat here
Be punctual
(Ancient Venture)
Where is the exit of the time
machine
Who knows
You can't make a mark at the
center of sea
Don't if any boat to rescue us
Ten billion years ago there's no
human being
Don't complaint
Help and think of something
Why don't you think
We don't have a Zonyi door
not even a bamboo dragonfly
Come to the venture without tool
it's all your fault
I want to clean my pocket from
time to time
Just right
Take half of it to fix
Can't help this
What kind of excuses is that ?
You don't have anything left?
I've got time belt
Kind of time machine ?
Then
we can go back to 20 century
If you want to go back
sure we can
Problem is where do you land
It can change time but not
location
Then it's no use at all
The small island can't be still
there on 20 century
And we'll be drown in the sea
You're so irresponsible
Take me here without any
preparation
Be quiet
Things all start from you
If you don't bring up
the request
Doraemon
Big discovery
Big enough to win Noble Prize
Found a fusel of fish and shell
behind school
This is very common
Fusel is common
point is my instinct's powerful
This is the new theory no one
ever think of
Will win a Noble Prize
Show me then
You listen well
Location found is several Km
away from the sea
Found the fusel of fish and shell
here
Means
In ancient time
Fish and shell lived on
the ground
Why do they live in the
sea now
Because, a hot weather like
today
They want to enjoy sun bath and
went to the shore
Sock in the water is very nice
then they decide to live there
Too bad
That's because long time ago,
here is still in the sea
No
10 billion years ago
Japan is connect to continent
Kuan don area is at the
bottom of the sea
Land can't be floating up and
sinking
It well. It takes many many years
Let's take the time machine and
see for ourselves
Ok, let's go
Here we are
Oh, no
Scare me, I didn't expect to
be in the sea
Look at Nobita
You see
At this time the shore is on the north
It's true
Then my new theory is going
down the drain
Don't be so disappointed
Since we are here
why don't we play for a while
The entrance of time machine
is the floating mark
Ya, ya
What a nice sky and ocean
Don't know what kind of fish
ancestor we can fish
It we take it back
everybody will be surprised
This is a big one
What a big fish
Help, help
Nobita, let go of the pole
I want to
but my hands can't relax
What should I do ?
Let it go, let go of it
Help
Wouldn’t come if I knew it
Will we starve to death here
Why don't we just
kill ourselves
What? Why are you suddenly ?
Someone is watching us from
the ocean
Shiny eyes
In the ocean?
Don't be bluffing
Wow, the island is moving
Help
I feel kind of weird since
just now
This is not an island
It's giant turtle
Giant turtle?
Yes, I've seen it in a book
It's called Bulo...Bulo
Bulo Kacasto
This is a Akalon kind
Then, this is carnivorous
It appears
Don't be panic
It's neck is so short
If we stay in the back of it
will be safe
It's diving into to the ocean
Doraemon, Doraemon
We are finished, finished
Hurry, use the time belt to go to
other time zone
Whatever will be better than
eaten by a turtle
This is the ocean of 20 century
No, it's not it
What are you doing in our pool
Yes, 10 billion years later this
is a land
We are safe, we are safe now
Hey, what are you doing ?
Why did you get in people's pool
Get out of there immediately
(Everywhere Canon)
Oh, no Oh, no
We'll be late
Wallet, wallet
Honey, my wallet
I'm going now
Briefcase, briefcase
Wait, honey, the briefcase
Honey
Oh,no
They bumped into each other
I can't catch the Singon Sian
What should I do ?
I'll be late for the important
business trip
Poor daddy
Think of something to help him
Everywhere Canon
Everywhere TV
Daddy, get in the canon
Get in there, and you'll be where
you want to
Hurry, daddy, get in there
Heysu
Then
which train station ?
Here
Going to fire now
I catch it
Thank goodness I catch the train
So cool
It can go anywhere ?
Just watch the screen, and that
is it
Let's get together
Send me over
Ok, this is simple
Come in
Heysu
Going now. Fire
Cool, so cool
Got it. I saw it
Ah, everybody look
Nobita, what happened to you?
Coming down from the sky
I flew here with the canon
Canon?
Yes, Doraemon is coming
with it
You see
this is it
So cool
Just like a real one
Did you really fly with this over
here?
Yes
Put the person or thing inside
It can send you wherever you
want to
Really wherever I want to?
You can all try
I'll be right over
Me too
I want to too, please wait
Shizuka, you are the first
Please take me to my father's
company
Thank you
This is really easy
Take the lunch box with you
Dial Shizuka's father company
That is the company
Going now
Fire
Getting into daddy's company
Ah, lunch box, my lunch box
But when did I bring it with me?
Look at daddy, he's so surprised
My turn next
I want to send the trash to some
place
This is not good to do that
No
It's ok, just a little bit
Ok
No, it's not good
Right, this is not good
It will cause trouble
Still not good
That way, everybody takes their
turns
Suneo did not do it yet
Suneo, what do you want to send?
I want to go traveling far far away
no matter where
A place far away
If you go alone, you can't come
back by yourself
So, my daddy and mommy are
going too
You see
Daddy?
Why are you not happy ?
That way, you can go traveling?
I have heard
Use this to send me abroad
I'm a bank robbery
Help me to go abroad quick
Move fast
I'm so impatient
Canon can't fire to the over sea
Then let me take the next flight
out
Hurry, or I'll shoot
I do it, I do it
That airplane is good
Ok, let me take that one
That is...
Be quiet, move fast
Get in here, that's all?
Fire
Yes
This way, I can escape safely
Yh, not at the air port
How can it be
finished
Broken
Whole week work
It took me a while to finish it
It's police...oh, no
Who did this ?
Don't run
I'm going to beat you into pieces
That's why I say no